<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Foodie</string>
    <string name="foodutar">Foodutar</string>
    <string name="open_nav">Open Navigation Drawer</string>
    <string name="close_nav">Close Navigation Drawer</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="eggette_pop_description">Welcome to Eggette Pop Delights &amp; More! We offer a delightful selection of treats at our bustling stall. Indulge in our signature Eggette Pops, crispy on the outside and fluffy inside. Dive into the flavors of Malaysia with our authentic Nasi Lemak or grab a quick, satisfying sandwich. Savor freshly baked bread and stay hydrated with ice-cold water. Join us for a culinary adventure that\'s sure to satisfy your cravings!</string>
    <string name="aunty_julia_cafeteria_description">Aunty Julia Cafeteria is a bustling food stall celebrated for its delightful array of Chinese mixed rice and an eclectic menu that satisfies a wide range of tastes. From the fragrant and spicy Nasi Lemak, to hearty plates of Fried Noodles and Fried Rice, each dish offers a taste of local tradition blended with Julia’s unique touch. The stall also features less conventional cafeteria options like fresh Salads and various Sandwiches, alongside the richly flavored Nasi Briyani.</string>
    <string name="cakers_inn_bakery_description">Cakers Inn Bakery is a delightful food stall that offers a diverse menu to satisfy various palates, making it a popular stop for both locals and visitors alike. Here, traditional favorites like the fragrant nasi lemak, savory fried noodles, and hearty fried rice stand alongside a selection of Western-inspired dishes such as fresh salads, various sandwiches, and freshly baked bread. For those looking for a quick, comforting meal, Cakers Inn also serves up steaming cup noodles, including a flavorful ramen option. Whether you are in the mood for something exotic or a comforting classic, Cakers Inn Bakery has something to cater to every taste.</string>
    <string name="charis_food_corner_description">Charis Food Corner is a delightful food stall that offers a variety of comfort foods organized into sets ranging from Set A to Set I. Each set is a thoughtful combination of dishes such as spaghetti, fried rice, a selection of fresh veggies, succulent chicken chop, and perfectly cooked eggs. This arrangement caters to a diverse palette, ensuring there are something to satisfy everyone—from pasta lovers and rice aficionados to those who prefer a lighter plate of vegetables or a hearty meat dish. Charis Food Corner is the go-to spot for delicious, well-balanced meals that feel like home-cooked comfort.</string>
    <string name="uncle_alan_vegetarian_description">Nestled in the bustling heart of the local food market, Uncle Alan Vegetarian offers a colorful and nutritious oasis for those seeking a wholesome meal. This charming stall, renowned for its vegetarian mixed rice, serves up a delightful array of expertly seasoned vegetables, fragrant tofu, and perfectly cooked grains. Each plate is a vibrant composition of textures and flavors, inviting both vegetarians and meat-lovers alike to indulge in a healthier dining option. With friendly service and a commitment to fresh, sustainable ingredients, Uncle Alan provides a tasty, guilt-free experience that nourishes the body and satisfies the soul.</string>
    <string name="cfour_noodles_stall_description">Nestled in the bustling heart of the local food market, CFour Noodles Stall is a vibrant culinary gem that caters to noodle lovers with its mouthwatering array of mee dishes. This bustling stall offers a delightful menu featuring its signature soup kari mee and dry kari mee, each dish brimming with bold flavors and aromatic spices that promise to tantalize your taste buds. Alongside its noodle specialties, CFour also serves a variety of refreshing beverages, making it the perfect spot to enjoy a satisfying meal and a cool drink in a lively, welcoming atmosphere. Whether you are in the mood for something spicy and soupy or tangy and dry, CFour Noodles Stall is your go-to destination for a truly delectable dining experience.</string>
    <string name="mcafe_economy_rice_stall_description">MCafe Economy Rice Stall offers a delightful selection of Chinese mixed rice dishes, skillfully combining savory chicken, succulent fish, and fresh vegetables to provide a hearty and balanced meal. Catering to diverse tastes, this stall is not just limited to rice; it also features a variety of beverages and sandwiches, making it a versatile spot for lunch or a quick snack. Whether you are in the mood for a traditional, comforting plate of mixed rice or a simple yet satisfying sandwich, MCafe provides tasty options that are both affordable and delicious, making it a favorite among locals and visitors alike.</string>
    <string name="next"><![CDATA[>]]></string>
    <string name="previous"><![CDATA[<]]></string>
    <string name="remember_me" />
    <string name="menu" />

</resources>